ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV)
1950-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 AV
115.28 cubic feet
110.2 linear ft.
Audio cassette tapes, open reel audio tapes, video cassette tapes, motion picture films.
7461791
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 31, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 08, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Scope and Contents
This collection contains video recordings, audio recordings, motion picture film, microfilm, and film strips collected, produced or otherwise created by the ILGWU. Among these are 3 DVD copies of 16mm film that document the celebration of the Union Health Center's 50th Anniversary in 1964. In addition to ILGWU members, staff, and officers, the event includes an address by President Lyndon B. Johnson.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Labor unions -- Clothing workers -- United States -- History; Clothing workers -- United States -- History; Clothing industry -- United States -- History
7461791
- When Wallace got the vote, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  16mm; 4.5 min.; AFL committee on public education harshly criticizes George Wallace in the 1968 election and warns agains voting for him in the 1972 election; criticizes policies in Alabma; 1972?; 2 copies
- Tellin' the World (Box 1, Folder 2)
  16mm; 9 min.; United Federation of Teachers talks about voter registration and participation for urban, working, and minority youth; Harold Mayer production
- COPE: Good Work for Democracy (Box 1, Folder 3)
  16mm; 25 min.; AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, labor's role in politics and legislation
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Shop time and motion study. Woman sewing garment with sewing machine. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Shop time and motion study. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Text in film: "hand assembly of screw caps, old method, assembling two operations causing excess handling and unbalanced distribution of work." "First operation, putting in, heavy lines in caps".
- Shop time and motion study. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Text in film: "cut out back lace, Miss Swank, March 1943, Management Engineering Department, ILGWU". Several women, cutting out a lace into a piece of cloth.
- Shop time and motion study., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  August-April; Text on film: "Flatlock Close, shoulder and sleeve, Belle Knitting Mills, November 1941, ILGWU Management Engineering Department. Followed by several women sewing what appear to be sleeves with sewing machines.
- Shop time and motion study. Several women doing several operations, such as, folding garments, sewing laces, sewing pocket darts, and bras, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  (missing); August-April; ILGWU Management Engineering Department
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop; time motion experiment in which several women sew laces into cloths. Automation, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop; time motion experiment in which several women sew darts and pocket dars, also bros and their respective cups. Automation, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  August-April; ILGWU Mangement Engineering Department
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  August-April; ILGWU Management Engineering Department
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  (missing) August-April; ILGWU Management Engineering Department
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shp. Automation, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Shop time and motion study. Compares 2 Factories, Taylor Style Efficiency Engineering Dept. Impartial Chairmens Office. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Text in film: "The Efficiency Engineering Department, of the Impartial Chairman, presents": "Comparisons." A film comparing 2 plants, one which has effective management and one which does not.
- Shop time and motion study. Woman ironing small pieces of cloth. (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Shop time and motion study. (Box 2a, Folder 41)
  Text in film: "Stretch, work, and cut gadget tape." Followed by a woman cuttinga long tape.
- Shop time and motion study. Film depicts lack of improvement in the Blossom Plastics stock room., 1950 (Box 2a, Folder 42)
  June
- Shop time and motion study., 1941 (Box 2a, Folder 43)
  August 7; Text in film: "stitch darts". Followed by women sewing and stitching darts.
- Shop time and motion study. (Box 2a, Folder 44)
  Text in film: "Work simplification management, engineering department". Followed by a woman sewing a large piece of garment. Film is torn and broken, perf damage
- Training film - various operations in garment production (Box 2a, Folder 45)
- Training films - various operations in garment production. (Box 2a, Folder 46)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Automation. (Box 2a, Folder 47)
  ILGWU Management Engineering Department.
- Training film - various operations in garment production. (Box 2a, Folder 48)
  (damaged)
- Shop time and motion study. Various operations in garment shop. Text in film: Learners Development of Skill. Women sewing. Automation. (Box 2a, Folder 49)
- Political action committee notes day jobs that need to be filled to accommodate voters: babysitting, transportation, reminder calls., 1950- 1959 (Box 2a, Folder 50)
- Union label commercials. Makeup and Rehearsals; S. Chaikin Visits Set., 1975 (Box 2a, Folder 52)
  Feb. 12
- Union label commercials. Makeup and Rehearsals; S. Chaikin Visits Set., 1975 (Box 2a, Folder 54)
- Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker; Grandmother and Granddaughter; The Bledsoes; Lillian, working mother. (Box 2a, Folder 55)
- Union label commercials. Emma; Retired Worker; Grandmother and Granddaughter; Half of the Bledsoes; Lillian, working mother. (Box 2a, Folder 57)
- Union label commercials (Box 2a, Folder 57a)
  2 Commericals; Lillian on both.
- Union label commercials. Lillian on Both. (Box 2a, Folder 58)
- Union label commercials. Lillian (Box 2a, Folder 58a)
- Union label commercials. Lillian on both. (Box 2a, Folder 61)
- Union label commercial spoofs. Laugh In (Box 2a, Folder 62)
  Meredith outdoor; Lydia indoor; J. Prine I indoor
- [no title] (Box 2a, Folder 63)
- Union label commercials. (Box 2a, Folder 63a)
  End Piece; Laugh In spoof
- [no title] (Box 2a, Folder 67)
- Misty Harbor; Union label commercials, 1980 (Box 2a, Folder 67a)
- Commercials - Union Label Makeup and Rehearsals; S. Chaikin Visits Set., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- [no title] (Box 3a, Folder 53)
- Union label commercials. "Commercials and Parodies" (Box 3b-c, Folder 64)
  2 copies
- Union label commercials. (Box 3d, Folder 64a)
  Jime prine I; Donny and Marie; Merv Griffin; Carol Burnett; Saturday Night live w/ American Dope Association
- "Report to the 1980 ILGWU Convention" (Box 4a-c, Folder 65)
  4 copies
- 9:1 (early version0; Report to the 1980 ILGWU Convention" (Box 4d, Folder 65a)
- Report to the Convention, 1983 (Box 4e, Folder 66)
  Reports ILGWU ad efforts from '76-'83, Archie Bunker, Barbara Mandrell, Bosom Buddies, Facts of Life, Dukes of Hazard, Harper Valley PTA Filthy Rich, Best of Carson, Gloria, Movies - "Paternity", "So Fine"
- [no title] (Box 4f, Folder 68)
- [no title] (Box 4g, Folder 69)
- [no title] (Box 4h, Folder 70)
- "Who Shoes Connnie"; "Whats Up", 1976 (Box 4I, Folder 71)
  (damaged; won't project); Feb.
- NBC News NY; Strike aversion agreement between management and ILGWU one hour before contract expires, 1976 (Box 4j, Folder 72)
  Feb.
- Misc. amateur film - recreation, tennis, dancing, eating, 1960-1979 (Box 4k, Folder 73)
  (Unity House?)
- Workmen's Circle home for the aged - groundbreaking festivities.Am (Box 4L, Folder 74)
  Amateur footage.
- Sixth annual outing at Unity House. General membership meeting at Hotel Diplomat, recreational activities, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- How to qualify and receive Social Security (Box 5a, Folder 76)
  In Spanish; US Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare; Social Security Admin; Bureau of Old Age and Survivors' insurance, creative arts studio
- Fall and Winter Fashions, 1960-1961 (Box 5b-e, Folder 77)
  4 copies; VHS version in Box 8
- Fall and Winter Fashions, 1961-1962 (Box 5f, Folder 77a)
- American Fashions, Fall-Winter, 1962-1963 (Box 6, 6a-c, Folder 78)
- Fashions. USA Consumer service program fashion and union label, 1963 (Box 6d-f, Folder 79)
  3 copies
- "A visit to the library", lessons 15 and 16 of "Speech Reading Film Text for Adults.", 1941 (Box 6g, Folder 80)
  (damaged; near the start); Created by BV Morkovin to assist adults learning to lip read.
- Fall and Winter Fashions, 1960-1961 (Box 6h, Folder 81)
- Outings to Unity House, includes Local 23., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  June 26-27
- Outings to Unity House, includes Local 23., 1954 (Box 7a, Folder 83)
  June 18
- Outings to Unity House, includes Local 23., 1955 (Box 7b, Folder 84)
  June 24
- Outings to Unity House, includes Local 23., 1952 (Box 7c, Folder 85)
  June 13
- Outings to Unity House, includes Local 23., 1956 (Box 7d, Folder 86)
- Misc. recreation - party with piata, dancing, dinner (Box 7e, Folder 87)
- Installation, Local 23 Ceremony, dinner banquet., 1953 (Box 7f, Folder 88)
  March
- Misc. recreation; Local 23 enjoys dancing. (Box 7g, Folder 89)
  (flim torn)
- Membership outing to Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 7h, Folder 90)
  Washington monument, Jefferson and Lincoln Memorials, Capitol Building, White House, Treasuring Building
- English as a Second Language (Box 7I, Folder 91)
  23 films, continuous loop
- Teleconference montage, N, 1983 (Box 7j, Folder 92)
  April; Live conference led by Frederick siems and Sol Chaikin; calls attention to damage to US garment workers and manufactureres caused by imports and non-reciprocal free trade. Encourages government tariffs against foreign-made garments
- Convention - Golden Jubilee, ILGWU, post event coverage, quotes speakers, resolution process, 1950 (Box 7k, Folder 93)
  David Dubinsky, Luigi Antonini, Oscar Ewing, Hubert Humphrey, Alexander Brody
- Fall and Winter Fashions, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  VHS
- English as a second language (Box 8, Folder 92-115)
  16mm; 23 films, continuous loop
- Meet your union: A film for new members. (Box 8, Folder 116)
  Office and Distribution Employees' Union Local 99, ILGWU.
- "Your Union: A film for new members." (Box 8, Folder 117)
  Skirt and Sportswear Workers, Local 23; 8 copies
- Local 32 events: Vacation check distribution, Unity House outing, maternity benefits, Christmas party. VHS called, Vacation Checks, 1951- 1952 (Box 8, Folder 133)
- Fashion 1960 (Box 8, Folder 136)
- Precincts people and power; Urging to volunteer for, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 134)
- Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration., 1964 (Box 9a, Folder 135a)
  16mm on cores; 7 min.; President Lyndon B. Johnson addresses the ILGWU at celebration of opening of Center, June 1964
- Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1964 (Box 9b, Folder 135b)
- Union Health Center 50th Anniversary celebration, 1964 (Box 9c, Folder 135c)
- The Fashion Picture (Box 9d-e, Folder 136)
  Spring-Summer, Union Label, production process bit; 2 copies; "Fashion 1960" on VHS in Box 8
- Jim Prine; Imports, Indoor Chorus, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Union label commercials
- Meredith Blouses; w/indoor Chorus, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Union label commercials.
- Emma Retired Worker, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Norma II/Outdoor, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Norma II/Outdoor Union label commercials
- Norma II/Indoor, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Oct. 15; Bledsoes w/Chorus, w/o Chorus, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Oct. 15; Bledsoes w/Chorus, w/o Chorus Union label commercials
- Bledsoes w/Chorus III, w/o Chorus III, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
- "Emma" Retired Worker, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- "Norma II Outdoor", 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Chorus III., Georgia, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- The Bledsoes, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Jim Prine II / w/indoor chorus, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Americans Helping Americans - Beverly, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Union label commercials, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Clothes in your Closet/ Kathy
- Union label commercials, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Clothes in your Closet/ Joan
- Union label commercials, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Americans Helping Americans - Beverly
- Jim Prine III (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Union Label commercials. Clothes in your closet/Joan, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  1" reel; 30 sec.
- Norma II / Indoor Chorus, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- "Song we Sing 3", 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Bledsoes w/ Chorus III and w/o Chorus III, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Jim Prine (original) - old chorus, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Norma II / Indoor Chorus, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Norma II / Indoor Chorus, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- The Bledsoes, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Norma II / Outdoor Chorus, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Closing Billboard, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Norma II / Outdoor Chorus (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Closing Billboard, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Emma - Retired Worker, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Retired Worker, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Song we Sing - 3, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Norma II / Outdoor Chorus, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Jim Prine II / w/ NEW indoor chorus, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Jim Prine II / w/indoor chorus, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Jim Prine II / w/indoor chorus, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 34a)
- Norma II / Outdoor Chorus, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Miami Composite for Kine, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Jim Prine II / w/ NEW indoor chorus, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 36a)
- Song we Sing; Voncile, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Bledsoes; indoor chorus, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Jim Prine II, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Jim Prine II, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Grandmother-Granddaughter, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Chorus 3 No C and Chorus 3 C, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Georgia w/ Chorus III, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Barbees - young couple w/ Lillian Chorus, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Jim Prine - imports; Phyllis Them - imports, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Closing Billboard (see also: f114), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Opening billboard, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Sterling Bank, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Opening Billboard, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Song we Sing, Helen, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Song we Sing, Joan, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Grandmother-Granddaughter II, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Phyllis Thiem, imports, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Lillian. Working Woman, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Grandmother-Granddaughter, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Barbees - young couple w/ Lillian Chorus, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Barbees - young couple w/ Lillian Chorus, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Jim Prine imports indoor chorus; Lydia, rough cut, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Norma II outdoor AND Norma II indoor, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Barbees - young couple, 1982-1986 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Phyllis Thiem imports, 1982-1986 (Box 15, Folder 62a)
- The Bledsoes, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Miss Liberty Slide, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  1" reel
- Opening shot, dub stock, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Presentation, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Statue of Liberty, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  1" reel; May 19, 1986
- Marvel Turkey (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Selected takes of "Georgia", 1982 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- The Taiwan Connection, Part 4, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 71a)
- Union Label commercials and "It Matters" parodies (Box 16, Folder 72)
  1" reel and VHS tape; One Day At A Time, WKRP, Commercial songs, Wheel of Fortune, AFL-CIO meetings with Irving Levine; Warwick Advertising "Crafted with Pride"; "It Matters--All Stars"; "It Matters--Sammy"
- Report to the Convention, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Report to the Convention, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Report to the Convention, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Original material (shots from Union Label commercials), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 76)
- Prot. Master Revised (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Report to the Convention, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  1" reel; September 20, 1980
- Original material, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  1" reel; 60 min.; October 23, 1984
- No description [may be presentations or footage from 1982 convention]. (Box 18, Folder 80)
- No description [may be presentations or footage from 1982 convention]. (Box 18, Folder 81)
- No description [may be presentations or footage from 1982 convention]. (Box 18, Folder 82)
- No description [may be presentations or footage from 1982 convention]. (Box 18, Folder 83)
- No description [may be presentations or footage from 1982 convention]., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 84)
- Paula Green Advertisement, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  1" reel; 50 min.; September 12, 1980
- Mixed slides and spots, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  1" reel; 50 min.; Septbmer 15, 1980
- Mixed voicces and effects, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  1" reel; September 22, 1980
- Various commercials, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 89)
- Paula Greene commercial, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 90)
- Paula Greene commercial, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 91)
- Paula Greene commercial, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 92)
- Paula Greene commercial, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 93)
- Convention, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  1" reel; 20 min.
- Convention, audio dub, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  1" reel; 15 min.
- Paula Greene presentation, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  3/4" reel?
- Musical performance, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  2" reel
- All's Fair, "True Confessions", 1976 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  3/4" U-Matic
- Mark Russell - makes a reference to the Union, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  (missing)
- Marilyn Socol sings Union Song on the Tonight Show, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 100)
- Union Label Commercial - Goldie Hawn and Liza, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 100a)
  Feb. 19; Song and Dance; Vaudevillian
- Union label commercial spoof. ILGWU Song in "Laugh In.", 1977 (Box 22, Folder 101)
- Toy Prods. "What's Happening" Show #201, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 102)
- Tonight Show, "Look for the Union Label.", 1977 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  January or December 2
- Union Label Song, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 104)
- Look for the Union Label; Family Feud., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 105)
- Merv Griffin Monologue., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 106)
- No Voer No Minimum, Formerly of Harletts, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 107)
- The Rag Business, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 108)
- LA Connection does union label song spoof. (Box 22, Folder 109)
- Tic Tac Dough., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 110)
- Singing union label Song, Match Game PM., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 111)
- Union Singers, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 265)
- MC Singing "Union Label" Song; Bowling for Dollars, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 112)
- Paul Lynde singing "Union Label" on Hollywood Squares., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 113)
- Paul Lynde singing "Union Label" on Hollywood Squares., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 114)
- Johnny Carson Segment., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 115)
- Lukehil Prods Make Me Laugh; Steve Bluesteins Minute with Celebrity Union Label piece., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 116)
- Alice and Flo sing Union Label Song., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 117)
- Me + Maxx (Maxx sings line of Union Label Song)., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 118)
- Mork and Mindy, Union Label. (Box 23, Folder 119)
- WKRP in Cincinnati, "The Union." (Box 23, Folder 120)
- Angry ILGWU Ladies Stampede Reagan's Cattle., 1985 (Box 23, Folder 121)
- "The Union", WKRP in Cincinnati., 1983 (Box 23, Folder 122)
- One Day at a Time, "Look for the Union Label." (Box 23, Folder 123)
- Phrase, "Look for the Union Label", Wheel of Fortune. (Box 23, Folder 124)
- Old Commercial Songs, TVs Bloopers and Practical Jokes. (Box 23, Folder 125)
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta Auditions 1. Union Label., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 126)
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta Auditions 2. Union Label (Box 24, Folder 127)
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta Auditions 3. Union Label. (Box 24, Folder 128)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 129)
  October
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 130)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 131)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions, "Imports", 1976 (Box 24, Folder 132)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 133)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 134)
- Union Label Chorus. California Auditions 1, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 135)
- Union Label Chorus. California Auditions 2, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 136)
- Union Label Chorus. St. Louis Auditions, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 137)
  August
- Union Label Chorus. Boston Auditions. ILGWU members, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 138)
  September
- Union Label Chorus. Boston Auditions. ILGWU members, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 139)
- Union Label Chorus. Dallas Auditions, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 140)
- Union Label Chorus. Dallas Auditions, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 141)